<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
<compression>None</compression>
<version>DarkSouls1</version>
<bigendian>False</bigendian>
<entries>
<text id="1000">SAVE DATA</text>
<text id="2000040001">Terms and Conditions</text>
<text id="2000040002">%null%</text>
<text id="2000040003">Accept</text>
<text id="2000040004">Decline</text>
<text id="2000040101">⑮：Scroll</text>
<text id="2000040102">⑮：Scroll ⑭：Select ⑲：Done</text>
<text id="2000040500">BANDAI NAMCO GAMES AMERICA INC.
DARK SOULS II: SCHOLAR OF THE FIRST SIN
END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT

IMPORTANT - READ CAREFULLY:  
Last Updated: December 22, 2014

This End User License Agreement (this “EULA”) may be updated from time to time. Your continued use of
the Game (as defined below) after a revised version has been communicated to you constitutes acceptance
by you of its terms.

THE GAME IS LICENSED TO YOU ON THE TERMS SET FORTH IN THIS EULA, WHICH CONSTITUTES
A LEGAL AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND BANDAI NAMCO GAMES AMERICA INC. (“BNGA”).  BY
ACCESSING, PLAYING, INSTALLING, OR OTHERWISE USING THE GAME IN ANY WAY, YOU AGREE
TO BE LEGALLY BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS EULA WITH BNGA.

THIS EULA CONTAINS, AMONG OTHER THINGS, AN ARBITRATION PROVISION CONTAINING A
CLASS ACTION WAIVER. 

The Dark Souls II: Scholar of the First Sin game, including, without limitation, any multi-player, online, or
downloadable portions thereof and any related written or electronic documentation or content (the “Game”),
is protected by domestic and foreign copyright laws as well as international copyright treaties and
conventions and other laws.  The Game is licensed, and not sold, and this EULA confers no title or
ownership to the Game or any copy thereof.  In addition to the terms and conditions hereof, when accessing
and using particular portions of the Game, including, without limitation, any multi-player, online, or
downloadable content, you may be subject to additional guidelines of third-party service providers.
</text>
<text id="2000040501">1. PRECONDITIONS OF THE LICENSES.  The licenses granted in this EULA are specifically conditioned
upon the following and your full compliance with all other terms and conditions set forth in this EULA:

a. You have reached the age of majority in your jurisdiction. If you are under the age of majority in your
jurisdiction, your legal representative (e.g., a parent or a person who has parental authority) must agree on
your behalf to comply, and take full responsibility for your compliance, with this EULA prior to your use of
the Game; 

b. You agree to and comply with all of the terms in this EULA, and any additional terms as may be
applicable to the Game, which acceptance is evidenced by your access to and use of the Game;

c. If the Game is provided through an online platform, you accept all applicable terms and conditions for
such platform, which acceptance is evidenced by your access to and use of the Game;

d. You access and use the Game only on local machines running validly-licensed copies of operating systems
on which the Game is designed to operate and which meet the minimum requirements set by BNG
(collectively, the “Hardware”); 

e. You do not use any hacks, cracks, bots, or third-party games that may modify, temporarily or permanently,
the code or the user experience of the Game, whether on your local machine or on servers that enable use of
any features of the Game.
</text>
<text id="2000040502">2. LIMITED USE LICENSE.  Subject to the terms of this EULA, BNGA grants you the non-exclusive,
non-transferable, revocable, limited right and license to access and use one copy of the Game solely for your
personal use with the Hardware.  Commercial use of the Game is prohibited.  To access and use the Game,
you must have legally obtained the Game from BNGA or an authorized third party distributor and all
Hardware and/or third-party products and services required to operate the Game and/or access any online,
multi-player, or downloadable portion of the Game that BNGA does not provide.  You are responsible for
paying all fees, taxes, and other costs you may incur to access and use the Game, including, but not limited
to, costs for any Hardware, Internet service, or other third-party products and services required to access
any multi-player, online, or downloadable portions of the Game.  Neither this EULA nor your access to or
use of the Game entitles you to any future releases of the Game or any expansions, sequels, or similar or
ancillary products. You have no interest, monetary or otherwise, in any feature or content contained in or
related to the Game.
</text>
<text id="2000040503">3. OWNERSHIP.  All intellectual property rights in and to the Game (including, but not limited to,
video, audio, and other content incorporated therein or later downloaded) and title to any and all copies
thereof are owned by BNGA or its licensors, and you receive no right or interest therein, except for the
limited licenses expressly provided herein.

You may not do any of the following:
• Copy the Game except for a single backup copy;
• Sell, rent, lease, license, distribute, or otherwise transfer or make the Game available to any other person,
in whole or in part, or use the Game or any part thereof in any commercial context, including, but not
limited to, on a commercial website or in a service bureau, "cyber cafe", computer gaming center, or any
other commercial location in which a user may access or use the Game who has not purchased or been
authorized by BNGA;
• Reverse engineer, derive source code, modify, decompile, disassemble, or create derivative works of the
Game or any online portion thereof, in whole or in part;
• Remove, disable, or circumvent any proprietary notices or labels contained on or in the Game or any online
portion thereof; or
• Export or re-export the Game or any copy or adaptation in violation of any applicable export restrictions or
other laws or regulations. 
</text>
<text id="2000040504">4. ONLINE MODES/SECURITY MEASURES/PROTECTIONS.
You will need an internet connection to connect to a game server(s) in order to play online modes of the
Game with other players. In addition, certain security measures may be required in order for you to make
full use of the Game, including, without limitation, the requirement to register the Game with a serial code,
the requirement to have continuous access to the Internet, and/or the acceptance of security/digital rights
management features.  Failure to accept the security measures may partially or completely impair your use
of the Game.
</text>
<text id="2000040505">5.  USER-GENERATED CONTENT.
 In exchange for access to and use of the Game and to the extent that you create content through access to
and use of the Game (“User-Generated Content”), you hereby grant BNGA an exclusive, perpetual,
irrevocable, royalty-free, fully transferable, and sub-licensable worldwide right and license to use
User-Generated Content in any way and for any purpose in connection with the Game and related goods and
services, including the rights to reproduce, copy, adapt, modify, perform, create derivative works from,
display, publish, broadcast, transmit, or otherwise use, distribute, exploit, and communicate to the public by
any and all means and media whether now known or hereafter devised without any further notice or
compensation of any kind to you for the whole duration of protection granted to intellectual property rights
by applicable laws and international conventions.  To the extent permitted by applicable law, you hereby
waive any moral rights of paternity, publication, reputation, or attribution with respect to BNGA’s and other
players’ use and enjoyment of such assets in connection with the Game and related goods and services under
applicable law.  The license granted to BNGA, and the above waiver of any applicable moral rights, shall
survive any termination of this EULA.
</text>
<text id="2000040506">6. ONLINE CONDUCT.  

6.1 BNGA does not pre-screen content of postings or online chats in the Game and does not assume any
responsibility or liability for User-Generated Content.  BNGA does not assume any liability for any failure to
remove, or any delay in removing, User-Generated Content.  Without limiting any of its other rights and
remedies under this EULA or applicable law, if BNGA objects to any User-Generated Content for any
reason, BNGA, in its sole discretion may (either itself or, if applicable, by request to a third-party service
provider): (a) remove the User-Generated Content; (b) give warnings to applicable persons; and/or (c)
restrict, suspend, or terminate access to and use of the Game without any notice or liability.  

6.2 You agree that you will be personally responsible for your access to and use of the Game, and for all of
your communication and activity in connection with the Game, including any User-Generated Content.  

6.3 You agree not to:
• Harass, threaten, embarrass, or do anything else to another user of the Game that is unwanted, as
determined by BNGA in its sole discretion. 
• Transmit or facilitate distribution of content that is harmful, abusive, racially or ethnically offensive, vulgar,
sexually explicit, defamatory, infringing, invasive of personal privacy or publicity rights, or objectionable, as
determined by BNGA in its sole discretion. Hate speech is not tolerated. 
• Violate any terms or policies communicated by BNGA from time to time.
• Promote or encourage any illegal activity, including hacking. 
• Disclose your own or other users’ personal information to third parties.
• Impersonate any person or entity, including any BNGA officials, forum leaders, guides, hosts, employees,
or agents, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity.
• Impede or disrupt the Game or the normal flow of Game play or dialogue or use vulgar language,
abusiveness, excessive shouting (e.g., ALL CAPS), "spamming," or any other disruptive or detrimental
methods in an attempt to disturb other users of the Game.
• Cheat or utilize unauthorized exploits in connection with the Game.
• Use or exploit any bugs, errors, or design flaws to obtain unauthorized access to or use of the Game or to
gain an unfair advantage over other players of the Game.
• Violate any applicable laws including, but not limited to, by posting, transmitting, promoting, or
distributing content that violates any applicable law or regulation. 
• Violate any rules for use of third-party technology and content, rules of interactive service providers, and
federal, state, local, and foreign laws where applicable.  Ignorance of the law is no excuse. 
• Do anything that interferes with the ability of other users to enjoy playing the Game in accordance with its
rules or that materially increases the expense or difficulty of BNGA or the third-party service provider (if
applicable) in maintaining the Game for the enjoyment of all its users.
• Intentionally disconnect from the network during online play or allow yourself to be defeated by a given
player repeatedly to help boost their rankings or win counts in the Game.
</text>
<text id="2000040507">7. LIMITATION ON DAMAGES.  

7.1 TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL BNGA, ITS
SUPPLIERS, ITS LICENSORS, OR THEIR RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES,
CONTRACTORS, OR AGENTS BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, EXEMPLARY,
PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER ARISING OUT OF THE POSSESSION OF,
ACCESS TO, USE OF, OR INABILITY TO USE THE GAME OR THE FAILURE TO PROVIDE SUPPORT
SERVICES, EVEN IF A PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.  THIS
LIMITATION WILL APPLY REGARDLESS OF THE THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER FRAUD,
MISREPRESENTATION, BREACH OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, PERSONAL INJURY, PRODUCTS
LIABILITY, INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY INFRINGEMENT, OR ANY OTHER THEORY. IN ANY CASE
AND EXCEPT AS OTHERWISE REQUIRED BY APPLICABLE LAW, BNGA'S, ITS LICENSORS’, AND
SUPPLIERS’ ENTIRE LIABILITY FOR ANY AND ALL DAMAGES UNDER THIS EULA SHALL BE
LIMITED TO THE AMOUNT ACTUALLY PAID BY YOU FOR THE GAME.   

7.2 BNGA AND ITS SUPPLIERS AND LICENSORS MAKE NO PROMISE OR WARRANTY THAT THE
GAME WILL WORK PROPERLY.  YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT BNGA AND ITS LICENSORS
AND SUPPLIERS ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR (A) ANY VIRUSES OR OTHER DISABLING
FEATURES THAT AFFECT YOUR ACCESS TO OR USE OF THE GAME, (B) ANY INCOMPATIBILITY
AMONG THE GAME, OTHER SERVICES, AND HARDWARE, OR (C) ANY DELAYS OR FAILURES YOU
MAY EXPERIENCE IN INITIATING, CONDUCTING, OR COMPLETING ANY TRANSMISSIONS OR
TRANSACTIONS IN CONNECTION WITH THE GAME IN AN ACCURATE OR TIMELY MANNER.  THE
GAME AND ALL OTHER SERVICES ARE PROVIDED “AS IS.”  EXCEPT AS DESCRIBED HEREIN [OR IN
OUR LIMITED WARRANTY ACCOMPANYING THE GAME.  BNGA AND ITS LICENSORS AND
SUPPLIERS EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS,
IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
BNGA does not ensure continuous, error-free, secure, or virus-free operation of any online, multi-player,
or downloadable portions of the Game or continued operation or availability of any given server.  Some
countries/regions do not allow limitations as to how long an implied warranty lasts and/or exclusions or
limitations of consequential damages, so the above limitations and/or exclusions of liability may not apply
to you.  This warranty gives you specific legal rights and you may also have other legal rights that vary from
country/region to country/region.

7.3 BNGA is not liable for any delay or failure to perform resulting from any causes beyond its reasonable
control.  Further, BNGA cannot and does not promise or ensure that you will be able to access the online,
multi-player, or downloadable portions of the Game whenever you want, and there may be extended
periods of time when you cannot access such portions of the Game.
</text>
<text id="2000040508">8. TERMINATION/SUSPENSION.

8.1 This EULA is effective upon your agreement to be bound by its terms and remains in effect until
terminated by you or BNGA.  You may terminate this EULA at any time by deleting and destroying any and
all copies of the Game in your possession, custody, or control. 

8.2 Except as otherwise prohibited by applicable law, BNGA may limit, suspend, or terminate the licenses
granted hereunder and your access to and use of the Game and any related services and products, at any
time and for any reason without notice or liability to you.

8.3 Without limiting any other rights of BNGA, if you fail to comply with the terms and conditions of this
EULA, BNGA retains the right, in its sole discretion, to immediately limit, suspend, or terminate your access
to and/or use of the Game.
8.4 Upon termination of this EULA, your rights to access and use the Game, including any licenses and
access to, if applicable, Game Currency, Virtual Items, user data, points, character progress, and any other
information of any kind related to the Game, will terminate immediately, and you must cease all use of the
Game.  In the event the Game is terminated, you must destroy all copies of the Game and all of its
component parts.

8.5 The termination of this EULA will not affect BNGA’s rights or your obligations arising under this EULA.
Those terms that by their nature are intended to survive this EULA shall survive this EULA.
</text>
<text id="2000040509">9. PRIVACY.  BNGA respects your privacy rights.  Any personal information supplied by you to BNGA online
or via any BNGA-controlled website will be subject to the privacy policy posted at:
http://www.BandaiNamcoGames.com/privacy. Notwithstanding what is stated in the applicable privacy policy,
if you use any online services, such as online play or the downloading and uploading of content, BNGA may
also collect, use, store, transmit and publicly display statistical data regarding game play (including any
platform ID, play log, play data (level, item), specifications of local machines, and residence regions), or
identify content that is created and shared by you with other players.
</text>
<text id="2000040510">10. U.S. GOVERNMENT RESTRICTED RIGHTS.  The Game has been developed entirely at private expense and
is provided as a "Commercial Computer Game" or "restricted computer Game." Use, duplication, or
disclosure by the U.S. Government or a U.S. Government subcontractor is subject to the restrictions set
forth in subparagraph (c)(1)(ii) of the Rights in Technical Data and Computer Game clauses in
DFARS 252.227-7013 or as set forth in subparagraphs (c)(1) and (2) of the Commercial Computer Game
Restricted Rights clauses at FAR 52.227-19, as applicable.  The Contractor/Manufacturer is BANDAI NAMCO
Games America Inc., 1740 Technology Drive, Suite 600, San Jose, CA 95110.
</text>
<text id="2000040511">11. INJUNCTION.  Because BNGA would be irreparably damaged if the terms of this EULA were not
specifically enforced, you agree that BNGA and/or its licensors and suppliers shall be entitled, without
bond, other security or proof of damages, to appropriate equitable remedies with respect to breaches
of this EULA, in addition to such other remedies as BNGA may otherwise have under applicable law.
</text>
<text id="2000040512">12. INDEMNITY.  You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless BNGA, its licensors, its suppliers, and
each of their respective officers, directors, employees, and agents from all damages, losses, and expenses,
including reasonable attorneys’ fees, arising, directly or indirectly, from any violation of this EULA by you or
from your acts and omissions to act in using the Game.  BNGA reserves the right to assume the exclusive
defense and control of any matter subject to indemnification by you.
</text>
<text id="2000040513">13. DISPUTE RESOLUTION/BINDING ARBITRATION/CLASS ACTION WAIVER.

YOU AND BNG AGREE TO RESOLVE ALL DISPUTES AND CLAIMS BETWEEN YOU AND BNGA IN
INDIVIDUAL BINDING ARBITRATION.  THAT INCLUDES, BUT IS NOT LIMITED TO, ANY CLAIMS
ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO: (A) ANY ASPECT OF THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN YOU AND
BNGA; (B) THIS EULA; OR (C) YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE GAME.  IT APPLIES
REGARDLESS OF WHETHER SUCH CLAIMS ARE BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT, STATUTE, FRAUD,
UNFAIR COMPETITION, MISREPRESENTATION, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY.

However, this Section does not apply to the following types of claims or disputes, which you or BNGA may
bring in any court with jurisdiction: (i) claims of infringement or other misuse of intellectual property rights,
including such claims seeking injunctive relief; and (ii) claims related to or arising from any alleged
unauthorized use, piracy, or theft.

This Section does not prevent you from bringing your dispute to the attention of any federal, state, or local
government agencies that can, if the law allows, seek relief from BNGA for you.

An arbitration is a proceeding before a neutral arbitrator, instead of before a judge or jury. Arbitration is
less formal than a lawsuit in court and provides more limited discovery.  It follows different rules than court
proceedings and is subject to very limited review by courts.  The arbitrator will issue a written decision and
provide a statement of reasons if requested by either party.  YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOU AND BNGA
ARE GIVING UP THE RIGHT TO SUE IN COURT AND TO HAVE A TRIAL BEFORE A JUDGE OR JURY.

You and BNGA agree to make reasonable, good faith efforts to informally resolve any dispute before
initiating arbitration.  A party who intends to seek arbitration must first send the other a written notice that
describes the nature and basis of the claim or dispute and sets forth the relief sought.  If you and BNGA do
not reach an agreement to resolve that claim or dispute within 30 days after the notice is received, you or
BNGA may commence an arbitration.  Written notice to BNGA must be sent via postal mail to: ATTN: Legal
&amp; Business Affairs Department, BANDAI NAMCO Games America  Inc., 1740 Technology Drive, Suite 600,
San Jose, CA 95110. 

The Federal Arbitration Act applies to this Section.  The arbitration will be governed by the Commercial
Arbitration Rules of the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”) and, where applicable, the AAA’s
Supplementary Procedures for Consumer Related Disputes, both of which are available at
http://www.adr.org.  The arbitrator is bound by the terms of this EULA. 

The AAA will administer the arbitration.  It may be conducted through the submission of documents, by
phone, or in person in the country/region where you live or at another mutually agreed location. 

If you seek $10,000 or less, BNGA agrees to reimburse your filing fee and your share of the arbitration
costs, including your share of arbitrator compensation, at the conclusion of the proceeding, unless the
arbitrator determines your claims are frivolous or costs are unreasonable as determined by the arbitrator. 
BNGA agrees not to seek its attorneys’ fees or costs in arbitration unless the arbitrator determines your
claims are frivolous or costs are unreasonable as determined by the arbitrator.  If you seek more than
$10,000, the arbitration costs, including arbitrator compensation, will be split between you and BNGA
according to the AAA Commercial Arbitration Rules and the AAA’s Supplementary Procedures for Consumer
Related Disputes, if applicable. 

YOU AND BNGA AGREE NOT TO BRING OR PARTICIPATE IN A CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE
ACTION, PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL ACTION, OR COLLECTIVE ARBITRATION, EVEN IF AAA’s
PROCEDURES OR RULES WOULD OTHERWISE ALLOW ONE.  THE ARBITRATOR MAY AWARD
RELIEF ONLY IN FAVOR OF THE INDIVIDUAL PARTY SEEKING RELIEF AND ONLY TO THE EXTENT
OF THAT PARTY’S INDIVIDUAL CLAIM.  You and BNGA also agree not to seek to combine any action or
arbitration with any other action or arbitration without the consent of all parties to this EULA and all other
actions or arbitrations.

If the agreement in this Section not to bring or participate in a class or representative action, private
attorney general action, or collective arbitration should be found illegal or unenforceable, you and BNGA
agree that it shall not be severable, that this entire Section shall be unenforceable, and any claim or dispute
would be resolved in court and not in collective arbitration. 

Notwithstanding this Section, you have the right to litigate any dispute in small claims court, if all the
requirements of the small claims court, including any limitations on jurisdiction and the amount at issue in
the dispute, are satisfied. 

This Section shall apply to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law.  If the laws of your jurisdiction
prohibit the application of some or all of the provisions of this Section, notwithstanding Section 15
(Governing Law), such provisions will not apply to you.

</text>
<text id="2000040514">14. GOVERNING LAW.  Any dispute not subject to arbitration, or where no election to arbitrate has been
made, shall be decided by the state of federal court located in Santa Clara County, California, and you and
BNGA agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of that court.  Except as otherwise set forth herein, this
EULA shall be governed by, and will be construed under, the laws of California and the United States of
America, without regard to choice of law principles. The UN Convention on Contracts for the International
Sale of Goods is expressly disclaimed.
</text>
<text id="2000040515">15. MISCELLANEOUS. If any provision of this EULA is held to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision
shall be struck and the remaining provisions shall remain in effect and be enforced as if the invalid or
unenforceable provision were not contained herein.  BNGA’s failure to act with respect to a breach by
you or others does not waive its right to act with respect to subsequent or similar breaches.  You may not
assign or transfer this EULA or your rights hereunder, and any attempt to the contrary is void.  This EULA
sets forth the entire understanding and agreement between BNGA and you with respect to the subject
matter hereof.
</text>
<text id="2000040516">If you have any questions concerning this EULA, you may contact BANDAI NAMCO Games America Inc.’s
customer service at http://www.bandainamcogames.com/support/ or BANDAI NAMCO Games America Inc.,
1740 Technology Drive, Suite 600, San Jose, CA 95110. </text>
<text id="2000040517">%null%</text>
<text id="2000040518">%null%</text>
<text id="2000040519">%null%</text>
<text id="2000040520">%null%</text>
<text id="2000040521">%null%</text>
<text id="2000050001">Information</text>
<text id="2000050002">Close</text>
<text id="2000050101">⑮：Scroll ⑲：Confirm</text>
<text id="2000060007">Offline Mode</text>
<text id="2000060008">%null%</text>
<text id="2000060009">%null%</text>
<text id="2000060010">Ver.</text>
<text id="2000060011">Calibrations</text>
<text id="2000070105">⑮：Select ⑭：Modify ⑲：Next ⑳：Back ①：Default</text>
<text id="2000070106">⑮：Select ⑭：Increase/decrease ⑲：Next ⑳：Back ①：Default</text>
<text id="2000080116">⑮：Select ⑭：Modify ⑲：Next ⑳：Back ①：Default</text>
<text id="2000080117">⑮：Select ⑭：Increase/decrease ⑲：Next ⑳：Back ①：Default</text>
<text id="2000090001">Creating save data.
Do not power off the system.</text>
<text id="2000110001">Data List</text>
<text id="2000110002">Level</text>
<text id="2000110101">Select a character to play.</text>
<text id="2000110102">Select a character to delete.</text>
<text id="2000110103">⑮㎎：Select ⑲：Confirm ⑳：Back ①：Info ②：Delete</text>
<text id="2000110201">You are about to delete this character.
Okay?</text>
<text id="2000110202">No more characters can be created.
Select a character to delete.</text>
<text id="2000110203">Delete the selected character and start a new game?</text>
<text id="2000110303">⑮㎎：Select ⑲：Confirm ⑳：Back ①：Info</text>
<text id="2000241500">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241501">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241502">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241503">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241504">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241505">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241506">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241507">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241508">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241509">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241510">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241511">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241512">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241513">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241514">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241515">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241516">%null%</text>
<text id="2000241517">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242500">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242501">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242502">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242503">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242504">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242505">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242506">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242507">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242508">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242509">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242510">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242511">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242512">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242513">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242514">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242515">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242516">%null%</text>
<text id="2000242517">%null%</text>
</entries>
</fmg>